Test:
CODE.
Message 1:
You can decode the second message by matching up the letters A and T for the cipher.
Message 2:
Go to the job listing you are applying for on our website (https://linxsystems.com/careers/5). Once you are on the job listing page, click anywhere on the page and type in "iwantajob".
Final message:
Good job! We hope you had fun with this challenge. To submit your solution, please send an email to careers@linxsystems.com with the subject line "LinxSystemsMobileJob". It is very important that this is the exact subject line that you enter, so we recommend copying and pasting to avoid any typos. Please create a secret gist (https://gist.github.com) with your code solution and include a url to your gist in the email. If you do this all correctly, you should receieve an email from us with a few questions that we would like you to answer. Please let us know if you do not receive the questionnaire.
